总会三明治 汉堡包
Club sandwich, burger.
憨 干嘛笑得这么开心
Why the big smile, Han?
是在兴奋灯芯绒裤里没穿内裤吗
You going commando under those corduroys?
不 麦克斯 我开心是因为
No, Max, I am happy today because
用餐顾客的整体质素终于有了提高
diner clientele has finally changed for the better.
瞧 靠墙桌子那边
Look, two parties of cool hipsters
坐着两帮嬉皮士潮人
are sitting at tables near wall.
你觉得那边坐着的是六个嬉皮士吗
You think those are six hipsters?
好吧 咱们再考一遍
Okay, let's go over this one more time.
-如何区分嬉皮士和流浪汉 准备好了吗 -好了
- Hipster or homeless pop quiz, ready? - Ready.
-嬉皮士穿什么 -紧身牛仔裤
- Hipsters wear? - Skinny jeans.
-流浪汉穿什么 -脏牛仔裤
- Homeless wear? - Dirty jeans.
-嬉皮士听什么 -收音机头的音乐
- Hipsters listen to? - Radiohead.
-流浪汉听什么 -自己头里的幻听
- Homeless listen to? - The voices in their head.
-嬉皮士有什么 -络腮胡和博客
- Hipsters have? - Beard and a blog.
-流浪汉有什么 -络腮胡和愁云惨雾
- Homeless have? - Beard and so much sadness.
我看见愁云笼罩着他和他
I see sadness, there and there.
我来搞定
I'll handle this.
我说过这家店不欢迎你们这种人
I told you before, I don't want you kind in here.
滚去追逐潮流吧
Take a trendy hike.
赶紧动身 苹果店十点就关门了
Better step it up. The Apple store closes at ten.
麦克斯 为什么你要把嬉皮士赶走
Max, why did you kick out the hipsters?
因为我不想再次成为
'Cause I could not be in the background
他们非主流自拍的人肉背景
of another Instagram photo.
这是最后一张账单 厄尔
Here's the last check, Earl.
麦克斯 那桌客人小费给得小气
And, Max, they stiffed us on the tip
却大方地忘了他们的相机
but they forgot their camera.
我会把它交给奥列格
Oh, I'll give it to Oleg.
他可以拍一张他的"独家"照片
He can take one of his special pictures.
这样的话 等他们回来取相机时
That way, when they come back to get it,
就能赏他们点小"鸡"瞧瞧
everyone will have been stiffed.
晚安 女士们
Well, good night, ladies.
我得在下雪之前到家
I gotta get home before the snow starts.
不会下雪的啦 厄尔 现在有十度呢
It's not gonna snow, Earl, it's 50 degrees.
肯定会下雪 相信我
Oh, it's gonna snow, trust me.
我猜不准我前妻何时会找上门
I couldn't tell when my first wife was coming,
但暴风雪上门 我可是一个说一个准
but I can sure tell when a storm is coming.
好吧 计划是什么
All right, so what's the plan?
如果真的下雪 我们该怎么办
What are we gonna do if it does snow?
你个死白妞 白雪遍地时我会弄丢你的
You're so white, I'm worried we're gonna lose you.
我喜欢下雪天
I love the snow.
打开我的阳台门 看着雪花飘落
Opening my balcony doors and watching it fall
就像全新的白色亚麻布
like fresh white linen and then
然后跑到对街的公园堆雪天使
running across the street to the park to make snow angels.
没错 那是你有钱时的下雪天
Yeah, that's snow when you're rich.
今年你唯一能看见的雪"天使"
The only snow angels you'll see this year
是六个在门廊前冻成冰的瘾君子
are the six crack addicts frozen to our stoop.
更不用说那只被我们非法
Oh, not to mention the adorable frozen horse
养在后院的可爱冰棍马
we have illegally living in the backyard.
麦克斯 不要这么夸张 栗宝没事的
Max, don't overreact. Chestnut's fine.
离下雪还几周时间呢
It's not gonna snow for weeks.
好吧 你就这么想吧
All right, have it your way.
但我可不想下一位房客
But I wouldn't want to be the next tenants
搞不懂为什么会有愤怒的马魂
who have to figure out why a pissed off horse
在布鲁克林的公寓阴魂不散
is haunting a Brooklyn apartment.
我冷死了 她却自以为是天气"砖"家
I was cold and she thought she knew weather patterns.
奥列格 存张你鸡鸡的倩影到这相机里吧
Oleg, take a picture of your junk on this customer's camera.
收到
Done.
你不问原因吗
Aren't you gonna ask why?
你有求 我必硬
No need.
我刚看见奥列格的...
I just saw Oleg's...
我得负部分责任
Yeah, that might have been my fault.
第一次见到 你震惊是正常的
Kind of a shock seeing it for the first time.
麦克斯 我不喜欢你暗示
Max, I don't like you implying
我可能会做出虐待栗宝的事
that I would ever be cruel to Chestnut.
我没有在暗示
I'm not implying it.
我是明示
I'm saying it outright.
现在可是冬天
It's winter.
我又不是没考虑过这个问题
And it's not like I've not been thinking about it.
但栗宝需要一个特别的家
But Chestnut belongs in a special home.
你才需要一个特别的家吧[精神病院]
You belong in a special home.
我查过了
I've done some research,
在大山峰公园有间休养所
and I found a retreat in the Grand Tetons
刚离婚的女人会去那里拥抱马儿
where newly-divorced women come to hug horses
帮助她们重建信任的能力
to help them gain back their ability to trust.
栗宝唯一相信的 是我这对"大山蜂"
The only Grand Tetons Chestnut trusts are mine.
小妞 赶紧面对现实吧
Lady, you gotta get a reality check real quick
厄尔说会下雪就真的会下
'cause Earl thinks it's gonna snow.
厄尔还觉得《黑街神探》的主题曲
Earl also thinks the theme from Shaft
是剽窃他在1975年寄出的录音样本呢
was stolen from a cassette tape he sent out in 1975.
把嘴闭上 真有其事
Shut your mouth. That happened.
麦克斯 不会下雪的
Max, it's not gonna snow.
我懂雪
I know snow.
我家在瑞士的萨斯费拥有一座小木屋
We owned a ski chalet in Saas-Fee Switzerland
这家餐馆也没人比我更了解
and I think I know more than anyone in this restaurant
如何在寒冷的气候下生存
about living in cold climes.
要下雪啦
Snow is coming.
喂 瑞士小妞 你想跟雪列格先生
Yo, Swiss miss, you wanna have a conversation about cold climes
聊聊寒冷的气候吗
with Snowleg over there?
麦克斯 我差点忘记了
Oh, Max, I almost forgot.
相机还你
The camera.
我想你一定会很满意
I think you'll be very pleased.
我还附赠了个精彩小短片哟
I made a little video as well.
为什么你要穿两件大衣啊
Why are you wearing two coats?
跟我戴两个套子一个道理
Same reason I wear two condoms.
免得有层破了
In case one breaks.
搞毛呀
What the?
早安 全世界最烂的天气预报员
Well, good morning, world's worst weather girl.
我这辈子没见过阳光如此"充足"的一天
I have never seen so much sunshine.
你知道这意味着什么吗
You know what that means?
《黑街神探》主题曲的确是厄尔写的
Earl wrote Shaft.
麦克斯 我知道下雪了 不劳你提醒
Max, I know it snowed, you don't have to tell me.
被这么多的白色包围 感觉就像阿尔·帕西诺
I'm surrounded by so much white stuff I'm like Al Pacino
在《疤面煞星》里的最后一幕
in the last scene of Scarface.
你穿的是什么呀
What are you wearing?
看起来像长出俩手臂的疯狂垃圾袋
You look like a bag of crazy garbage grew arms.
这是2011年冬季家用品混搭系列
It's the Hefty 2011 winter collection.
我把大衣给栗宝了
I gave Chestnut my coat.
这是让雪不落在我身上的唯一办法
This is the only way to keep the snow off me.
瞧瞧可怜的栗宝
Look at poor Chestnut.
他蹄子裹的是什么
What is he wearing on his hooves?
我把我名牌山羊绒的袜裤剪了给它穿
I cut up my Fendi cashmere leggings.
上次我们潜入别墅时顺手抓的
I grabbed them when we raided the town house.
我当时只想着自己 忘了他了
I thought ahead for me, but not for him.
让他穿女人衣服 他尊严何在啊
He is humiliated in those ladies clothes.
他看起来像埃德加·胡佛
He looks like J. Edgar Hoover.
我凌晨四点就出来扫雪了
I've been out here sweeping since 4:00 A.M.
但雪一直下
But it just keeps coming down.
你他妈有病啊 雪花
What is your problem, snow?
我以前多爱你呀
I used to love you!
或许我们该问问你以前的门童
Maybe we should ask your old doorman
"这里插入统称的爱尔兰人名" 来帮忙
"insert generic Irish name here" to come help.
我知道他们的名字
I know their names.
日班詹姆斯 夜班詹姆斯和黑人詹姆斯
Day James, night James and black James.
你的计划就是一直扫雪扫到开春
So your plan is you're gonna sweep the snow away till spring
扫到他被雪活埋了还在扫吗
while the horse is trapped under this tarp?
而且这块防水布是附近那家
Which I'm pretty sure was covering the out of business
倒闭的古巴饭馆的顶盖吧
Cuban restaurant down the street.
他们倒闭了 我留了张纸条
They were out of business and I left a note.
上面写什么 "我是疯子 多谢"
What did it say? "I'm loco, gracias."
不 我是写"抱歉拿了你屋顶 撑着点"
No, it said, "Sorry I took your roof, hang in there.:
麦克斯 不要这么消极
Max, don't be so negative.
管这布是哪儿来的 管用就行了
Doesn't matter where it came from, it's working.
我再固定一下这块布就行了
I just need to secure this tarp a little.
打住 你是想蹬着高跟鞋
Stop, you were gonna climb on an icy chair
爬上结冰的椅子 然后摔断脖子吗
in six inch heels and break your neck
然后害我得养着穿袜裤的马
and then I'm gonna be stuck with a horse in leggings
和嘴里叼着筷子坐轮椅的你
and you in a wheelchair with a chopstick in your mouth
还用筷子打信号 "抱歉 我以为能行的"
tapping out, "I'm sorry, I thought that would work."
我在博爱居家当义工时
I learned to build when I volunteered
学过盖东西
with Habitat for Humanity.
回想起来 那些穷人比现在的我富多了
Looking back, they had so much more than I have now.
好吧
Okay.
我得去当保姆了
I gotta go to my babysitting job
等我回来 你和我得坐下来
and when I get back, you and I are gonna sit down
好好商量出一个靠谱点的家
and come up with a more realistic home
给小变装癖马
for J. Edgar Hoofer.
麦克斯 他就住在这儿
Max, he lives here.
相信我 这行的
And I'm telling you, this is working.
我这法子其实蛮聪明的呢
What I'm doing is actually kind of brilliant.
现在我开始担心你盖的那些房子了
Now I'm worried about those houses you built.
你好 琵琪
Hey, Peach.
麦克斯 我有个天大的好消息
Max, I have the most incredible news.
律师终于发现婚前协议书的漏洞了吗
Lawyer finally found a loophole in your prenup?
我也希望 但不是
I wish, no.
我刚接到电邮通知
I just got an email
我成功晋级到
and I have made it to the final round
《三角洲主妇》选角的最后一轮了
of casting for Real Housewives of Tribeca.
《三角洲主妇》啊
Real Housewives of Tribeca?
现在连普通小区都能成为主题了吗
They're doing neighborhoods now?
那之后是要做《这里到那里主妇》吗
What's next, Real Housewives of from here to there?
布莱德和安洁莉娜
and I want everything to be perfect
得呈现最完美的一面给人家看
when they see Brad and Angelina.
琵琪 你不觉得你的孩子
Uh, Peach, are you aware that your children
被衣服包得喘不上气吗
are being eaten by clothing?
这个儿童防雪服可是国际大牌呀
The snowsuits are Burberry.
而且包起来就看不出安洁莉娜的肥胖
And the padding hides Angelina's weight problem.
够了 你别再这么说了
Okay, you have to stop saying that.
她才没有体重问题
She doesn't have a weight problem.
她一年胖了11公斤呢
She's gained 25 pounds in one year.
没错 因为她的体重是从0开始
Yeah, 'cause she started at zero.
麦克斯 我们必须得呈现最好的一面 因为
Max, we all have to look our best, 'cause ready?
这节目还是我和米斯提·马斯特鲍的较量
The last spot in the show is between me and Misty Mastbaum.
我以为她是你闺蜜呢
I thought she was your bestie.
她是啊 但我的闺蜜是贱人
She is, but my bestie's a bitchy.
她超级好胜
She's crazy competitive.
节目刚有谱
As soon as we were approached about the show,
她就领养了三条腿的狗 还取名为泡菜
she adopted a three-legged corgi and named it Mr. Pickle.
那还真是很超级贱啊
That's crazy bitchy.
所以现在 我要找残疾的动物
So now, I'm looking up handicapped animals
你想要只残疾的动物吗
Oh, you want a handicapped animal?
我可以帮你弄来
I got your handicapped animal.
我知道一匹有分辨性别障碍的流浪马
I know a homeless horse with gender identity issues.
我是想要一些可爱点 但有缺陷的
I was thinking something cute, but damaged.
比如法国独眼斗牛犬
Like a one-eyed French bulldog.
要是这匹马以前是匹明星马呢
What if I told you that this horse was a celebrity horse?
继续说
Tell me more.
我朋友 卡洛琳·钱宁
My friend, Caroline Channing...
你怎么会认识卡洛琳·钱宁啊
How do you know Caroline Channing?
她是我戒酒互助协会的保证人
She's my AA sponsor.
的确有可能
Makes sense.
继续
Go on.
总之 这匹可爱但是超有缺陷的马是她的
Anyway, she has this cute, but crazy damaged horse
她的生活从天堂掉下地狱后
and since her life flipped upside down,
那马需要一个好的归属
he needs a good home.
我得先见见卡洛琳·钱宁
Well, I'd have to meet Caroline first.
周六把她带这儿来
Bring her by on Saturday.
麦克斯 这个主意太棒了
Max, what an amazing idea.
米斯提就乖乖受死吧
Misty is literally going to die.
我真高兴你酗酒过度
I am so thrilled you have a drinking problem.
你非得把他放我卧室吗
Did you have to put him in my bedroom?
你房间最容易布置"马匹保护措施"
It was the easiest room to horse proof.
毕竟里面没值钱物品
You have so little of worth.
你不用在谷歌上搜了 我已经
You can stop googling. I already found
找到完美的下家了
a perfectly good place to put him.
你不会想着让我把栗宝交给琵琪吧
You're not still suggesting I give Chestnut to Peach Landis?
麦克斯 看着我 看着我的眼睛
Max, look at me. Look at me in the eyes.
你嗑药嗑傻了吗
Are you high?
没有 你乱弄我房里的东西后
No, I couldn't find my bedroom stash
我就找不到我的"药"了
since you moved everything around.
栗宝需要的是一个有爱的家
Chestnut needs a home with affection
琵琪连抱自己的孩子都不愿意
and Peach won't even hug her children.
她雇你来代劳
She pays you to do that.
所以才完美呀
That's why it's perfect.
华丽的马房她出钱
She'll pay for the fancy stable
我们还可以随心所欲地去抱栗宝
and we'll go and hug Chestnut for her whenever we want.
你只需去见她一面 然后这事就成了
You just need to go meet her and it's done.
我是天生的富家女
I have the DNA of a rich girl,
即使我现在和你躺在廉价公寓的床上
even though I'm lying in bed with you in a tenement
还用了硬币去买晚餐
and I bought my dinner tonight with dimes.
我和栗宝是老派富人
Chestnut and I are old money.
老派富翁不会到处炫耀自己
And old money doesn't parade itself around
在摄像机前显摆求关注
in front of cameras and beg for attention.
不光你有老钱
Hey, you're not the only one with old money.
我口袋里也有个
I've had a dollar in my jeans
揣了三周的老硬币
I've been carrying around for three weeks.
你周六去见琵琪
You're meeting Peach Saturday,
我们就跟那匹马说再见了
and we're saying good-bye to the horse.
送走栗宝对你来说就这么容易啊
Why is getting rid of Chestnut so easy for you?
难道你小时候没养过宠物吗
Didn't you ever have a pet as a child?
养过 我有只小狗
Yes, I had a puppy.
跟我妈妈住了一周后
And after a week of living with my mom,
她就开车把我跟小狗都扔路边了
she pulled the car over and put us out on the side of the road.
她把狗弄走了啊
She got rid of it?
听着 宠物不是我的菜
Look, pets are not my thing, okay?
我已经有个又黏人又毛绒绒
I already have something needy and fluffy
不照顾就会死掉的东西 就是你
that'll die if I don't take care of it... you.
快去 到你去看他了
Go, it's your turn to go check on him.
不要 上次我过去 抓到他偷吃我胸罩呢
No, I went the last time and caught him eating my bra.
别夸大其词 他只吃了一半
Don't exaggerate. He only ate half of it.
抱歉 你说得对 我应该持乐观态度
Oh, I'm sorry, you're right, I should be more positive.
我的罩"杯"是半满的
One of my cups is half full.
里面发生什么事了
What's going on in there?
我想你应该不会
I don't suppose there's any way
在梳妆台上拉一大坨屎吧
you took a giant dump on your dresser?
你不能怪栗宝 他可能是不安
You can't blame Chestnut. He's probably nervous.
穿上你的袜裤之后
After wearing your leggings,
他一直准备着一举成名的试镜呢
he's getting ready for his fame audition.
他是个疯子 从手到脚都是
He's a maniac, maniac on all fours.
麦克斯 有发现
Oh, Max, here's something.
布鲁克林的艾薇马房
The Ivy bridge riding stables in Brooklyn.
离这儿只有五英里远
Only five miles away.
他们的网站上说 他们的马
It says on their website that their horses
能在广告和电影中出镜
are featured in commercials and films!
栗宝说不定能出演《战马》续集呢
Can you say Chestnut, star of the War Horse sequel?
你是不是偷抽了我床头柜的大麻
Did you take the weed from my bedside table?
看着我
Look at me.
看着我的眼睛
Look at me in the eyes.
你嗑药嗑傻了吗
Are you high?
老实说
Honestly...
有点儿
a little.
关掉电脑 快睡觉吧
Close that and go to sleep.
不 我还在看
No, I'm still reading.
瞧 我刚弄出了你的浏览记录
Oh look at that, I just pulled down your browser history.
挺耐人寻味啊
Interesting list.
小猫弹电子琴
Kitten plays a keyboard,
小猫边打喷嚏边放屁
kitten sneezes and farts at the same time?
给我 那可是我的隐私
Give me that, that's private.
小猫折衣服
Kitten folds a T-shirt!
小猫按门铃
Oh, kitten rings a doorbell.
我还以为宠物不是你的菜呢
I thought you said you weren't into pets.
我是不喜欢
I'm not!
但这可是小猫按门铃啊
It's a kitten ringing a doorbell!
他想用人类的方式进门
He's trying to get in like people.
你对可爱动物明明就没有抵抗力
You have a secret soft spot for animals.
不 我只喜欢奇怪的小猫
No, I'm just into freaky kittens.
还有个影片是小猫穿上蛇皮西装
There's one who puts on a snakeskin suit
然后去出差呢
and goes on a business trip.
这不是可爱 这是奇怪
That's not soft. That is freaky.
好吧 你让我去帮栗宝找个现实的下家
Fine, you're telling me to get a reality check about Chestnut.
但你也需要回到现实
But you need one too.
他走后你一定会想他的
You're gonna miss him when he's gone.
麦克斯 你有在听吗
Max, are you listening?
麦克斯 别担心
Max, don't worry.
我知道明天去马房
I know it's all gonna work out perfectly
绝对会进展顺利
at the stables tomorrow.
我没有在担心
I'm not worried.
那人还没来呢
The man's not here yet.
靠 转回去 我们得重新进场
Damn it, turn us around Max, we have to enter again.
这都是第三遍了
This is the third time.
拜托嘛 麦克斯 跟奥列格借大衣
Max, come on, we borrowed these coats from Oleg
不就是为了巨星般的入场吗
to make a dramatic star entrance.
如果你想让我再假[高潮]一次
If you want me to fake it again,
你得请我吃饭 叫我美人儿
you have to buy me dinner and call me pretty.
好吧 那快帮忙放我下来
Fine, then help me down quickly.
我不想下马的丑样被马房的人撞见
I don't wanna be mid-dismount when the stable guy walks in.
天啊
God, ugh.
你刚坐到我脸上了
You just sat on my face.
好像我还没有"受"够一样
Like I haven't done enough for you.
你好 请问你是汤尼吗
Oh, hello, are you Tony?
没记错的话 我是
Last time I checked.
天啊
Oh, jeez.
我是卡洛琳·钱宁 我们通过电话
I'm Caroline Channing. We spoke on the phone.
他是栗宝
And this is Chestnut.
麦克斯 往后退
Max, step back.
很好 我就去那边
Oh, great. I'll just be over here
跟《桂冠幼童》节目背景里
like the awkward father in the background
尴尬的父亲一样站着
on Toddlers and Tiaras.
主角在这儿
Well, here he is.
我们谈过的 栗宝是只冠军跳栏马
And as we discussed, Chestnut is a champion jumper
他的马术表演无懈可击
his dressage is impeccable,
他在马术表演赛上得过三次奖
he's ribboned three times at the Hampton Classic,
血统来自十分精英荟萃
and he comes from a historically elite line
的表演马家族
of distinguished show horses.
他尿起尿来跟镇暴水柱一样威猛
And he pees like a civil rights fire hose.
麦克斯 再往后退退
Max, step further back.
得了 咱们就打开天窗说亮话吧
Come on, let's cut to the chase.
他是匹好马 棕色 穿袜裤的样子超恶心
He's nice, brown, he looks sick in leggings,
他还不要钱 要不要随便你
and he's free, so take him or leave him.
你说他是什么时候的跳栏马
When'd you say he was a jumper?
2005至2010年
From 2005 to 2010.
他以前可是有专人指导的呢
He was in a class by himself.
或许他过去是个跳栏马
Well, maybe he was a jumper,
但他已经廉颇老矣了
but he isn't anymore.
什么
What?
他身材有点走样了
Well, he's a little out of shape.
你丫的有种啊
Well, you have a gut.
别激动 我只是说他曾勇猛过
Whoa! I'm just saying he's seen better days.
我也只是说你曾不秃过
I'm just saying your hair is falling out in fistfuls.
好了 好了
Okay, okay.
别搞人身攻击 这生意还得谈呢
Let's not get personal, we all want this to work.
他这么说栗宝
He's the one who's getting personal
才是人身攻击吧
going after Chestnut like that.
好吧 那你告诉我
Okay, you tell me,
他上一次运动是什么时候
when's the last time he's exercised?
你上一次运动又是什么时候
When's the last time you exercised?
看来娱乐界不好混呀
Wow, show business is rough.
好了 你是汤尼 对吧
All right, it's Tony, right?
没记错的话 是的
Last time I checked.
汤尼 你必须得原谅她
All right, Tony, you'll have to forgive her.
她真的很爱这匹马 并希望这能谈成
She really loves him and wants this to work out.
重点是 天下没有免费的马
Bottom line is, even a free horse isn't free.
养他要钱 照顾费神
I still have to feed him and take care of him
而老实说 这匹马给我赚不来一个子儿
and truth be told, this horse isn't gonna make me a penny.
电影合作商过来 肯定也是选那匹靓马
If my film guy comes in here, he's gonna pick that beauty
而不是这匹
over this one.
所以这事谈不成 姑娘们
So it's not gonna work out, girls.
好吧 你不要还有别人要呢 死胖子
All right, well, we got other offers, fatty.
来 咱们走
Come on, let's go.
下次你害人穿着借来的有毒
You know, maybe next time before you let someone
又带廉价古龙水味的皮毛大衣
ride five Miles across Brooklyn in a toxic, Russian,
骑了五英里穿过布鲁克林时
cologne-soaked rent-a-fur,
你应该搞搞清楚 电影业
you should be clear that the film business,
即使选马 也偏爱有年纪跟精英血统的
even for horses, is ageist and elitist.
没错 我们的确是走下坡的老将
And, yes, we may have seen better days,
但只要努力与决心和一点点运气
but with hard work, determination and a little luck,
谁说老将就不能再上巅峰
one day we'll be back on top.
对了 你的大明星马根本就无聊到爆
Yeah, and I'm not impressed by your big star pony overthere.
只会傻站着一动不动
He's just standing still.
要想打动我的心
You wanna impress me?
让他学猫叫 然后去按门铃吧
Have him meow and ring the doorbell.
别放在心上 栗宝
Don't take it personally, Chestnut.
那些马都是整形的
Those horses have had work done.
在见琵琪之前 把垃圾袋肚兜脱了如何
Maybe you wanna take the cinch sack off before you meet Peach.
不必 外面在下雪 而我还是个穷光蛋
No, it's snowing again and I'm a penniless beggar.
那就应该打扮得像点
I should look like one.
再说了 她可能会以为这是时尚打扮呢
Besides, she'll probably think it's a look.
好吧 我知道跟琵琪见面
All right, I know this one on one
不是你理想中的场景
with Peach isn't your ideal scenario,
但一切都是为了栗宝
but it's what's best for Chestnut,
所以打起精神 面对现实吧
so man up and face reality.
你说得对
You're right.
我的朋友 卡洛琳·钱宁
And my friend, Caroline Channing...
怎么了
What is it?
你可能已经做好准备面对现实
You might be ready to face reality,
但你准备好要面对现实版的真人秀了吗
but are you ready to face reality TV?
这地方充斥着琵琪版的克隆人
The place is crawling with Peach clones
和准备拍你的电视摄像机
and TV cameras ready to meet you.
她完全是挖坑给咱们跳
She totally set us up.
你开什么玩笑
Are you kidding me?
太妙了 这太棒了 真是太棒了
Fabulous, this is awesome, just awesome.
她利用卡洛琳·钱宁的潦倒奇葩样
She's using the Caroline Channing freak show
来让她进另一个奇葩秀
to get herself on another freak show.
好吧 你说得对 咱们走 你不必进去
All right, you're right, let's go, you don't have to do this.
不 如果栗宝因我得游街示众
No, if I made Chestnut parade around
在电视上被人当笑话看
and be humiliated in public,
我也愿意接受同样的待遇
then I have to be willing to do the same.
给 拿着我的"大衣"
Here, hold my coat.
你一直随身带着这些吗
You always have those with you?
是啊 我可是从曼哈顿来的
Yes, I'm from Manhattan.
-好了 说"感谢您大驾光临" -什么
- Okay, thank me for coming. - What?
感谢您大驾光临 当我还是亿万富翁的时候
Thank me for coming, that's what people did all the time
别人常对我说
when I was a billionaire.
感谢您大驾光临
Thank you for coming.
不 感谢您邀请我
No, thank you for inviting me.
哇 太牛了
Wow, that's so cool.
淡定点
Don't freak out.
我要一秒钟变富家女了
I'm about to get my rich on.
我们进去后 我需要介绍你吗
So when we go in there I'll introduce you?
不必
Oh, you don't have to.
有钱人总是假装
Rich people always pretend
认识彼此
to know each other.
现在打开门
Now open that door,
让我帮栗宝找个家
and let's get my baby a home.
琵琪
Peach.
我想感谢你邀请我来你这么漂亮的家
I wanna thank you for inviting me into your beautiful home
在我这非常困难艰苦的时期
and showing me such kindness
对我伸出援手
during this very difficult, difficult time.
女士们 我正式向大家介绍
Ladies, I would like you all to meet
我亲爱的朋友 卡洛琳·钱宁
my dear friend, Caroline Channing.
在她经济上非常困难艰苦的时期
Who, in light of her recent very difficult, difficult
她请我收养她残疾的宠物马
financial troubles, has asked me to adopt her damaged pet horse
这还是我的酒鬼仆人麦克斯帮牵的线
who was brought to my attention by my alcoholic servant, Max.
她在那边
Right over there.
卡洛琳
Caroline,
感谢您大驾光临
thank you for coming.
不 感谢你的邀请
No, thank you for inviting me.
我为你感到骄傲
I'm proud of you.
是我为你感到骄傲
No, I'm proud of you.
搞得我又浑身起鸡皮了
I just got the chills again.
麦克斯 你瞧他
Oh, Max, look at him.
他在笑呢
He's smiling.
他喜欢这地方
He likes this place.
是啊 也快值得你在真人秀上被人羞辱了
Yeah, it's almost worth you being humiliated on reality TV.
我不会出现在那节目上的
Oh, I'll never be on that show.
我没有签授权书
I didn't sign the release.
什么
What?
老派富人不会随便签名
Old money don't sign.
你会喜欢这儿的 对吧
You're gonna love it here, huh?
你是不是会喜欢这呀
Aren't you gonna love it here?
又好又大的马房
A nice big stable.
我可能喜欢 也可能不喜欢
Maybe I will, maybe I won't.
也许我该跟我的挚友麦克斯回家住
Maybe I should come home and live with my best friend, Max.
那卡洛琳怎么办
What about Caroline?
她可以睡在防水布下
She can sleep under the tarp.
我猜你找到你的大麻了
So I guess you found your weed.
不 我和栗宝单独相处时 都这么玩
No, this is just something we do when we're alone together.
这是我们的小秘密
It's kind of our thing.
你真的很爱栗宝 对吧
You really love Chestnut, don't you?
还好啦
He's all right.
他又不是猫咪
He's no kitten.
好吧 我们很快会再见的 栗宝
Okay, I'll see you soon, Chestnut.
你想单独跟他待会儿吗
You want a minute alone?
我在外面等你
I'll be out front.
我知道这些话可能有点可笑
This is probably gonna seem ridiculous to you
因为你只是匹马 而我只是某个
because you're a horse and I'm just some lady
在过去几个月一直喂你胡萝卜的女人
that's been slipping you carrots for the last few months, but...
我真的爱上你了
I really got attached to you.
这待遇可是其他马儿没有的
This is way more than most horses get out of me.
罐装巧克力豆停产那会儿 我都没这么难过
I wasn't even this upset when they discontinued tan M&Ms.
我...
I, um...
我这一生有许许多多的不如意
I really haven't had much go right for me in my life,
我也确信未来只会愈加艰难
and I'm pretty sure things are gonna keep getting worse but,
可你却如此的好
you were a good thing.
当一切都不如人意时
And when everything sucked,
你是我们生活中唯一的美好
you were the best thing we had going.
而且你还毛绒绒的
And you're fuzzy too.
你超毛茸茸的 而且谁敢说
You're so fuzzy, and no one can argue
摸着一个暖融融毛绒绒的东西不有爱啊
that touching a warm, fuzzy thing isn't straight up lovely.
感谢你给我们带来的一切
So, thank you for everything you did for us, but...
尤其是长得这么毛绒绒
especially for being fuzzy.
麦克斯 你还好吧
Max, are you okay?
嗯 我没事 我绝不会有事
Yeah, I'm fine, I'll always be fine.
你在哭吗
Are you crying?
是的 我在哭
Yeah, I'm crying,
因为我也想住在这里
'cause I wish I could live here.
别担心 我们可以来看他
Don't worry, we'll come visit,
我们会想到法子 等春天来了就带他回家
and we'll find a way to bring him home in the spring.
好啦 我有满满一口袋铜板呢
Come on. I have a pocket full of dimes.
我们去买点便利店玉米卷
Let's go get some convenience store taquitos
配着蓝覆盆子酒 大快朵颐一番吧
and wash 'em down with blue raspberry wine coolers.
杂货店在特卖呢
They're on sale at the bodega.
八瓶只要五块
Two four packs for five dollars.
你还真懂怎么让伤心的姐妹打起精神
You know exactly what to say to cheer a broke sista up.
等回到家 给你看个小猫
And when we get home, I found a video
他会唱火星哥的歌呢
of a kitten singing Bruno Mars.